Guide to the Richard Finkel Associates records, 1946-1987 and undated RL.11675
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Richard Finkel Associates records
1946-1987 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Finkel, Richard
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11675
15.0 Linear Feet
Advertising executive based in Seattle, Washington; specialist in newspaper advice columns and cartoon advertisements. Collection includes clip art, cartoon and comic designs, advertising copy, print advertisements and other largely humorous printed materials that feature advertising characters, limericks, "do it yourself" hints and advice columns, and fact- and quiz-based promotional copy. Newspaper advertising services were primarily directed at local businesses including apparel and shoe stores, appliances and home furnishings, automotive dealerships and service firms; hardware stores, hotels and restaurants, insurance and real estate companies, sporting goods and travel agencies primarily in the Pacific Northwest and Canada. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Copy Drafts, Cartoons, and Punch Lines; Local Newspaper Attraction Series; Offset Print Blocks; Printed Material; Sample Sets; Scrapbook Pages; and Special Rewrites.
Biographical / Historical
Advertising executive based in Seattle, Washington; specialist in newspaper advice columns and cartoon advertisements.
Born 1918, Vancouver, Canada. 1936: Writer, Canadian Publishing Company. 1939: Advertising, Vancouver News-Herald. 1939-1941: Free-lance advertising copy writer; radio news program, CKMO; Sales representative, Malva Mfg. (food products). 1941-1945: Public relations and radio programming, Royal Canadian Air Force. 1946: Copy writer and account planning, Stewart-Lovick Ltd. advertising agency; Junior Chamber of Commerce, Vancouver. 1947: Advertising manager, Campbell Motors car dealership. 1948: Sales partner in an automobile dealership network. 1949: Moved to the United States; Promotion Manager, California Farmer magazine, San Francisco. 1952: Open Richard Finkel Advertising agency, Seattle. 1955-1962: Artcraft Features, a newspaper syndicate service. 1964: Territory Manager, Warner-Lambert Company (Richard Hudnut, Lactona product lines). 1970: Artcraft Features renamed Panorama Features as a joint enterprise between Richard Finkel & Associates, Richards & Roberts; and Lanson-Brooks agencies. Panorama eventually acquired by BBDO.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Richard Finkel Associates records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2005.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. Bertram Metter papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements
Jim Brown papers
John W. Crawford papers
Leo Bogart papers
Wright H. Everett papers.
Collection Overview
Advertising executive based in Seattle, Washington; specialist in newspaper advice columns and cartoon advertisements. Collection includes clip art, cartoon and comic designs, advertising copy, print advertisements and other largely humorous printed materials that feature advertising characters, limericks, "do it yourself" hints and advice columns, and fact- and quiz-based promotional copy. Newspaper advertising services were primarily directed at local businesses including apparel and shoe stores, appliances and home furnishings, automotive dealerships and service firms; hardware stores, hotels and restaurants, insurance and real estate companies, sporting goods and travel agencies primarily in the Pacific Northwest and Canada. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising, Newspaper; Wit and humor in advertising -- United States; Advertising -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Cartoons (humorous images); Newspapers; Advertising -- Automobiles; Advertising -- Clothing and dress; Advertising -- Hotels; Advertising -- Restaurants -- United States; Advertising -- Tourism; Travel; Advertising -- Insurance; Real estate business -- United States; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- General files, 1946-1982 and undated; 1
  - Business cards and tags, undated; 1 folder (Box 1)
  - Clients/contacts business cards, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence and testimonials, 1979-1981 (Box 1)
  - Inventory lists, 1975-1982 (Box 1)
  - Letterhead, stationery, undated (Box 1)
  - Panorama Features--Advertising, brochures, etc., undated (Box 1)
  - Panorama Features--Cartoon samples by series on microfiche, undated (Box 1)
  - Panorama Features--Presentation flip book, undated (Box 1)
  - Panorama Features--Promotional scrapbook, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Richard Finkel resume, biographical sketches, undated (Box 1)
  - Richard Finkel Advertising--Samples of advertising copy, 1946-1953 and undated (Box 1)
  - Sample advertising, notes, etc., 1975 and undated (Box 1)
- Copy drafts, cartoons, punch lines, etc., undated; 2
  - ABC of Beauty, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising sketch, undated (Box 24)
  - Advertising cartoons, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising cartoons, undated (Box 24)
  - Advertising cartoons, comics, limericks, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Apparel, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Appliance stores, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Automotive, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Drug stores, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Fashion Tips from Jan, undated (Box 23)
  - Advertising examples--Hotels, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Insurance and real estate, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Restaurants, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Shoe stores (English and French), undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising examples--Sporting goods, undated (Box 2)
  - Advertising ideas sample sets by product category, undated (Box 2)
  - Automotive advertising cartoons, undated (Box 2)
  - Automotive advertising cartoons, undated (Box 23)
  - Bath, plumbers, undated (Box 2)
  - Becky's Corner (Consumer advice), undated (Box 2)
  - Camera and You/Camera Tips, undated (Box 2)
  - Camera columns (contents of album), undated (Box 2)
  - Car columns, undated (Box 2)
  - Carpet Care Tips, undated (Box 2)
  - Charm Chat, undated (Box 2)
  - Charm Chat and other related columns, undated (Box 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes Beauty Hilights; Your Beauty Is My Business; Fashion Focus; Women's Fashion Tips
  - Classified advertisement cartoons (Ad Laffs), undated (Box 2)
  - Clip art samples, undated (Box 2)
  - Cowboy series, undated (Box 2)
  - Decorating Tips, undated (Box 2)
  - Do It Yourself series, undated (Box 2)
  - Dry cleaning, undated (Box 2)
  - Editorial advertising, newspaper column advertising, undated (Box 2)
  - Facts of Life/Facts By (your name), undated (Box 2)
  - Facts of Life/Facts By (your name), undated (Box 23)
  - Financial Tips, undated (Box 2)
  - Flower Lore (Say It with Flowers), undated (Box 2)
  - Food Facts (Food for Thought), undated (Box 2)
  - Footwear (Foot Notes, Harry the Shoe Man), undated (Box 2)
  - Gardener's Corner, undated (Box 2)
  - Headline advertising, undated (Box 2)
  - Helpful Hints, undated (Box 2)
  - Henry, undated (Box 2)
  - Hollywood Hannah, undated (Box 2)
  - House plants, undated (Box 2)
  - How's Your IQ?, undated (Box 2)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 3)
  - Insurance--Cartoons, undated (Box 3)
  - Insurance--Extended Coverage, undated (Box 3)
  - Insurance--Quotes, undated (Box 3)
  - Insurance--Suzie series, undated (Box 3)
  - Jewelry, jewelers, undated (Box 3)
  - Josephine, undated (Box 3)
  - Josephine, undated (Box 23)
  - Laff Lines, undated (Box 3)
  - Laff Lines, undated (Box 23)
  - Last Laugh, undated (Box 3)
  - Last Laugh, undated (Box 23)
  - Linoleum Sam, undated (Box 3)
  - Little Ads, undated (Box 3)
  - Little George, undated (Box 3)
  - Little George, undated (Box 23)
  - Little Gordon, undated (Box 3)
  - Men's fashion, undated (Box 3)
  - Menuettes, undated (Box 3)
  - Menuettes, Miles of Smiles, undated (Box 23)
  - Musical Notes, undated (Box 3)
  - Nationalities, undated (Box 3)
  - Nationalities, undated (Box 23)
  - New real estate cartoon series, undated (Box 3)
  - New Travel Reporter, undated (Box 3)
  - Occupations, undated (Box 3)
  - Occupations, undated (Box 23)
  - Oozoo, undated (Box 3)
  - Paint and wallpaper, undated (Box 3)
  - Pets: Fact and Fancy, undated (Box 3)
  - Pharmacy Facts, undated (Box 23)
  - Pharmacy Health Tips, undated (Box 3)
  - Pharmacy Reporter, undated (Box 3)
  - Pharmacy Reporter, undated (Box 23)
  - Quotations, undated (Box 3)
  - Real estate, undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Real estate, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Real Estate Q&A, undated (Box 3)
  - Recipe of the Week, undated (Box 3)
  - Safe and Sound, undated (Box 3)
  - Sally Forth, undated (Box 3)
  - Sally Forth, undated (Box 23)
  - Sewing series, undated (Box 3)
  - Short Circuit, undated (Box 3)
  - Short Circuit, undated (Box 23)
  - Silhouettes (Small ads for drug stores), undated (Box 23)
  - Sports Facts/Sports Quiz, undated (Box 3)
  - Steppin' Out, undated (Box 3)
  - Steppin' Out, undated (Box 23)
  - Thrill Her, undated (Box 3)
  - Tips from (your name), undated (Box 3)
  - Toilet cartoons, undated (Box 3)
  - Travel Advisor, undated (Box 3)
  - Travel cartoons, undated (Box 3)
  - Travel cartoons, undated (Box 23)
  - Travel Reporter, undated (Box 3)
  - Travel Reporter, undated (Box 23)
  - Wallpaper, undated (Box 3)
  - Weekly Health Tips, undated (Box 3)
  - Weekly Tip, undated (Box 3)
  - What Is It?, undated (Box 3)
  - Window Treatments, undated (Box 3)
  - Would You Believe It?, undated (Box 3)
  - Yes Sir series, undated (Box 3)
  - Yes Sir series, undated (Box 23)
- Local Newspaper Attraction series, undated; 3
  - A New Approach--A Newspaper Column, undated (Box 4)
  - Audio and Stereo Facts, undated (Box 4)
  - Automobile Limericks, undated (Box 4)
  - Better Language, undated (Box 4)
  - Bible-related, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Brad Breezy, undated (Box 4)
  - Camera Comments, undated (Box 4)
  - Camera Tips, undated (Box 4)
  - Car Care, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Carpet Care Tips, undated (Box 4)
  - Charm Chat, undated (Box 4)
  - Charm Chat and other related columns, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Includes ABC of Beauty; Josephine; Little George; Cartoons; Sally Forth; Occupations; Drawings (What Is It?)
  - Clip art--Canadian, undated (Box 4)
  - Clip art--Canadian; Headlines; Furniture; Women, undated (Box 5)
  - Clip art--Furniture, undated (Box 5)
  - Clip art--Headlines for Special Occastions; Women; Furniture, undated (Box 5)
  - Clip art--Women, undated (Box 5)
  - Cowboy series, undated (Box 5)
  - Decorating Questions and Answers, undated (Box 5)
  - Decorating Tips, undated (Box 5)
  - Do It Yourself series, undated (Box 5)
  - Do It Yourself/Helpful Hints, undated (Box 5)
  - Dress for Success, undated (Box 5)
  - Dress for Success/Dress to Win, undated (Box 22)
  - Facts of Life, undated (Box 5)
  - Fashion Tips, undated (Box 5)
  - Flower Lore (Say It with Flowers), undated (Box 5)
  - Food Facts (Food for Thought), undated (Box 5)
  - Gardener's Corner, undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
    Includes Houseplants; Pets: Fact and Fancy
  - Gardening, undated (Box 6)
  - Headlines clip art, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Helpful Hints, undated (Box 6)
  - House plants, undated (Box 6)
  - How's Your IQ?, undated (Box 6)
  - Insurance cartoons, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Insurance headlines, undated (Box 6)
  - Insurance/How's Your IQ?, undated (Box 6)
  - Jewelry (An Expert Talks About)/Tips From Your Jeweler, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Laff Lines, undated (Box 6)
  - Language, undated (Box 6)
  - Last Laugh, undated (Box 6)
  - Let's Talk Dry Cleaning, undated (Box 6)
  - Man About Town (A Man's Opinion), undated (Box 6)
  - Men/Menuettes/Steppin' Out/Laff Lines, undated (Box 6)
  - Men's Fashion Notes, undated (Box 7)
  - Menuettes, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Miles of Smiles, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Nationalities, undated (Box 7)
  - New Real Estate Q&A, undated (Box 7)
  - Oozoo, undated (Box 7)
  - Pharmacy cartoons, undated (Box 7)
  - Pharmacy Reporter, undated (Box 7)
  - Real estate, undated (Box 7)
  - Real estate cartoons, undated (Box 7)
  - Real estate columns, undated; 3 folders (Box 7)
    Includes Real Estate Q&A; Illustrated; Headlines; Children; Insurance cartoons
  - Real Estate Q&A, undated (Box 7)
  - Safe 'n Sound, undated (Box 7)
  - Sewing columns, undated (Box 7)
    Includes Needle Notes; Sewing Tips
  - Short Circuit, undated (Box 8)
  - Short Circuit/Facts of Life, undated (Box 8)
  - Short Circuit/Facts of Life/Linoleum Sam, undated (Box 8)
  - Silhouettes (Small ads for drug stores), undated (Box 8)
  - Smart Sayings, undated (Box 8)
  - Sports Quiz, undated (Box 8)
  - Sports Quiz/Language/Oozoo/Smart Sayings, undated (Box 8)
  - Steppin' Out, undated (Box 8)
  - Suzie Says, undated (Box 8)
  - Travel cartoons, undated (Box 8)
  - Travel Reporter, undated (Box 8)
  - Wallpaper, undated (Box 8)
  - Weekly Health Tips, undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Weekly Tip (A Man's Opinion), undated (Box 8)
  - Women's columns, undated (Box 22)
    Includes Women's Fashion Tips; Fashion Focus; Fashion Tips; Dress to Win
  - Women's shops (Charm Chat), undated (Box 8)
  - Would You Believe It?, undated (Box 9)
  - Yes Sir series, undated; 3 folders (Box 9)
    Includes Miles of Smiles; Car Talk; Steer This
- Offset print blocks, undated; 4
  - Josephine, undated (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 24)
  - Pharmacy Reporter, undated (Box 10)
  - Travel Reporter, undated (Box 10)
- Printed material, 1971-1987 and undated; 5
  - Alaska Airlines brochure, 1981 (Box 11)
  - American Express Gold Card direct mail, 1986 (Box 11)
  - American Gem Society roster 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Arlington (Wash.) Times rate card, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Artcraft Features promotional booklet, undated (Box 11)
  - Buyer's Market Want Ads, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Classified International Advertising Services booklets: Automotive; CAM (Classified Advertising Manager); Telemarketing, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Classified International Advertising Services--Go for the Green in Classified clip art and layout book, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Dynamic Graphics Inc.--Clipper/PMS service brochure/catalog, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Fortune Magazine--In Advertising, As in Journalism, Cartoons the Most Effective Means of Putting Across Ideas, undated (Box 11)
  - Herald (Snohomish County, Wash.) rate card, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Homes Magazine examples, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Issaquah (Wash.) Press rate card, 1986 (Box 11)
  - John Bartholomew and Son--Historical Map of England and Wales, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Metro Associated Services--A.D. in Action, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Metro Associated Services--Metro's Plus Business, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Metro Newspaper Service--Advertising layout idea book, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Multi-Ad Services--Kwikee Ad-Builder Mini Book, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Multi-Ad Services--Services for Manufacturers, 1984 (Box 11)
  - National Systems-Ad Ideas--Appliance Stores, 1986 (Box 23)
  - North Snohomish County Express Shopper rate card, undated (Box 11)
  - Pemco Insurance--The Shield no. 6 newsletter, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Print Media Service--Special Trial Issue advertising layout ideas, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Purdy Painting Tools--The Ten Commandments of Brush Care, Usage, and Value, undated (Box 11)
  - Retail Ad Week, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Retail Reporting Bureau--Retail Ad Week direct mail, undated (Box 11)
  - Retail Reporting Bureau--Retailing Library direct mail, undated (Box 11)
  - Safeco Title Insurance brochure (Pink Panther cartoon), 1979 (Box 11)
  - SCAN (Selective Classified Advertising for Newspapers) direct mail, 1987 (Box 11)
  - SCW Services--Advertising Idea Book, 1987 (Box 24)
  - SCW Services--Bride's World, 1986 (Box 23)
  - SCW Services--Pet Care, 1986 (Box 23)
  - SCW Services--Timely Topics, 1987 (Box 23)
  - SCW Services miscellaneous (Quik-Art, clip art library offers), 1987 (Box 11)
  - Seattle Water Department--Water Conservation Kit direct mail, undated (Box 11)
  - Skagit Valley Herald advertising supplement--Skagit Valley in Bloom, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Warehouse Shoe Outlet flyer, 1986 (Box 11)
- Sample sets, undated; 6
  - ABC of Beauty, undated (Box 11)
  - Answers to 10 Tough Painting Questions, undated (Box 11)
  - Automobile Limericks, undated (Box 11)
  - Better in Every Language, undated (Box 11)
  - Camera Tips, undated (Box 11)
  - Car Care columns, undated (Box 11)
  - Car Care Tips, undated (Box 11)
  - Carpet Care Tips, undated (Box 11)
  - Cartoons, undated (Box 11)
  - Charm Chat, undated (Box 11)
  - Clip art, undated (Box 11)
  - Clip art--Furniture, undated (Box 11)
  - Clip art--Headlines for Special Occastions, undated (Box 11)
  - Clip art--Women/Fashion, undated (Box 11)
  - Decorating Tips, undated (Box 11)
  - Do It Yourself, undated; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Do You Remember?, undated (Box 11)
  - Dry cleaning, undated (Box 11)
  - Facts of Life 1-52, undated (Box 12)
  - Fashion Tips, undated (Box 12)
  - Financial Tips, undated (Box 12)
  - Gardener's Corner, undated (Box 12)
  - Hair care copy, undated (Box 12)
  - Headlines, undated (Box 12)
  - Headlines--Insurance, undated (Box 12)
  - Headlines--Real estate, undated (Box 12)
  - Helpful Hints, undated (Box 12)
  - Humor, undated (Box 12)
  - Insurance--Cartoons, undated (Box 12)
  - Insurance--Suzie series, undated (Box 12)
  - Jewelry, undated (Box 12)
    Series A: An Expert Talks About; Series B: Tips from Your Jeweler
  - Josephine, undated (Box 12)
  - Laff Lines, undated (Box 12)
  - Last Laugh, undated (Box 12)
  - Little George, undated (Box 12)
  - Man About Town (A Man's Opinion), undated (Box 12)
  - Menuettes, undated (Box 12)
  - Miles of Smiles, undated (Box 12)
  - Nationalities, undated (Box 12)
  - New headlines--General 1-52, undated (Box 12)
  - New real estate columns, undated (Box 12)
  - New real estate Q&A 1-105, undated (Box 12)
  - New Steppin' Out series 1-52, undated (Box 12)
  - Occupations, undated (Box 12)
  - Oozoo, undated (Box 12)
  - Pharmacy Reporter, undated (Box 12)
  - Real estate, undated (Box 12)
  - Real estate columns, undated (Box 12)
  - Real estate headlines, undated (Box 13)
  - Real estate limericks, undated (Box 13)
  - Real Estate Q&A, undated (Box 13)
  - Sally Forth, undated (Box 13)
  - Short Circuits, undated (Box 13)
  - Silhouettes (Small ads for drug stores), undated (Box 13)
  - Smart Sayings, undated (Box 13)
  - Sports Quiz 1-52, undated (Box 13)
  - Steppin' Out, undated (Box 13)
  - Tips from Your Jeweler, undated (Box 13)
  - Travel cartoons, undated (Box 13)
  - Travel Reporter, undated (Box 13)
  - Weekly Health Tips, undated (Box 13)
  - What Is It?, undated (Box 13)
  - What's New in Real Estate?, undated (Box 13)
  - Windows and draperies, undated (Box 13)
  - Women's Fashion Tips, undated (Box 13)
  - Yes Sir series, undated (Box 13)
- Special rewrites, undated; 7
  - Abrams Chevrolet (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Advance TV and Stereo (Winnipeg), undated (Box 13)
  - Almvig's (Seattle), undated (Box 13)
  - Bank of Arlington (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Bessey's Electric Service (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Bothell Appliance and TV (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Butcher restaurants (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Canasco Bonham Insurance (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Creswell Electric (Oregon), undated (Box 13)
  - Garber Buick (Michigan), undated (Box 13)
  - Garber Shoe Stores, undated (Box 13)
  - Gordon's Auto Parts (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - H&H Shoes (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Hainstock Men's Wear (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Headlines--Insurance and real estate, undated (Box 13)
  - Headlines--Two Extra, undated (Box 13)
  - Hub Electric (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Last Laughs--Men's shoes, undated (Box 13)
  - Lusk Brake and Alignment Service (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Macie's Boot and Western Wear, undated (Box 13)
  - Mackay Forest Products (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Morgan's (Calif.), undated (Box 13)
  - Morse Motors, undated (Box 13)
  - Neepawa Ford Mercury (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Nelson Office Machines (Wash.), undated (Box 13)
  - Oceanair (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - People's Motors (Iowa), undated (Box 13)
  - R.H. Davis & Co. (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Rock Island Tape Centre (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Seally's Shoes, undated (Box 13)
  - Theodore's shoe stores, undated (Box 13)
  - Tire shop, undated (Box 13)
  - Valley Stationers (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Vanessa Fashion Shoes (Canada), undated (Box 13)
  - Vern Jeffreys (Aqua-Epoxy), undated (Box 13)
  - Walser Travel Service, undated (Box 13)
  - World Travel Service, undated (Box 13)
  - Yould's (Canada), undated (Box 13)
- Scrapbook pages, undated; 8
  - Automotive, undated (Box 14)
  - Cartoon advertising, undated (Box 14)
  - Cartoon advertising, undated; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Customer relations/Public relations advertising, undated (Box 15)
  - Do It Yourself, undated (Box 16)
  - Facts/Facts of Life, undated (Box 17)
  - Fashion and jewelry, undated (Box 17)
  - Gardening--Gardener's Corner, undated (Box 17)
  - Hair care and beauty salons, schools, undated (Box 18)
  - Headline advertising, undated (Box 18)
  - Helpful Hints, undated (Box 18)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 19)
  - Music columns, undated (Box 19)
  - Newspaper columns--Do You Remember, undated (Box 19)
  - Real estate, undated (Box 20)
  - Restaurants and hotels, undated (Box 19)
  - Sally Forth, undated (Box 19)
  - Shoe stores, undated (Box 19)
  - Sports Quiz, undated (Box 19)
  - Travel/Travel Tips/Travel Reporter, undated (Box 21)